Santiago Sabogal Agredo

Santiagoagredo@live.com

Bogotá D.C, Colombia

Profile:

Web developer with extensive work experience in bilingual customer service. I am analytical and have skills in efficient problem solving, organization, results orientation, assertive communication, and attention to detail. I like to acquire knowledge and I enjoy challenges. I am extremely patient and I accept feedback in the best way.

Portfolio

https://santiagredo.github.io/PersonalPortfolio/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/santiago-sabogal-266525247/

Education:

Platzi / 06/2021 - Present

Frontend and Backend development school with JavaScript.

Certificates: https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1NN3lg4g13O-cZxG1KTqLNv9jSUnRZXbp?usp=sharing

Misión TIC 2022 / 06/2022 - 12/2022

Python Programming Fundamentals, Basic Java Programming, FullStack Development with Java, JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

Certificates:

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1ocnodve5sDURaPq3EtXoW60nUoOrl-p5?usp=sharing

Fundación Ana Restrepo del corral (Sena) / 01/2015 - 12/2016

Technician in Accounting and Financial Operations Management.

Work experience:

24/7 Intouch / Bilingual agent-12/2021 - Present

Support agent for Airbnb, in charge of helping with payments, reservations, refunds for guests and hosts around the world.

Teleperformance, Usaquén / Bilingual agent - 09/2020 - 10/2021

Hotel support agent for Expedia, in charge of helping with reservations, advance payments, credits to travelers, and basic technical support on the payment and reservation platform of the company and hotels.

Calzilla, Toberín / Bilingual agent - 01/2019 - 03/2020

Customer service agent for GUESS, in charge of tracking packages and placing orders, complaints and refunds. Experience in calls, emails and chats for the same company.

Convergys, Usaquén / Bilingual agent - 01/2017 - 09/2017

AT&T customer service and technical service agent, I was in charge of making payments for prepaid telephone plans and provided support when their mobile connections or telephones did not work properly.

Languages: -Spanish: Native

-English: Advanced

Hobbies:

-Boxing

-Cycling

-Reading

-Any activity that is physically or psychologically stimulating.